At fourteen, they made a pact to rock together forever. They meant it.
Anvil! The Story of Anvil is a documentary, music
film directed by Sacha Gervasi.
At 14, best friends Robb Reiner and Lips made a pact to rock together forever.
Their band, Anvil, hailed as the "demi-gods of Canadian metal" influenced a
musical generation that includes Metallica, Slayer, and Anthrax.
Following a calamitous European tour, Lips and Robb, now in their fifties, set off to
record their 13th album in one last attempt to fulfill their boyhood dreams.
Self - Lead Guitar, played by Steve 'Lips' Kudlow.
Self - Drummer, played by Robb Reiner.
Self, played by Kevin Goocher.
Self, played by Glenn Gyorffy.
Self, played by William Howell.
Self - Manager, played by Tiziana Arrigoni.
The Story of Anvil is a 2008 Canadian rockumentary film
about the Canadian heavy metal band Anvil.
The film is directed by screenwriter Sacha Gervasi, in his directorial debut, and features interviews with other
musicians who have been influenced by the band, including Slash, Tom Araya, Lemmy, Scott Ian, and Lars Ulrich.
The film explores themes of friendship, heavy
metal, rock band, hard rock, 1980s.